<tool>单词：tool
意义：
   n.   器具，工具；（有助于做工或完成某事的）用具；受人利用的人；压印机；
   vi.   使用工具；开车，乘车；
   vt.   用工具给…加工；压印；驾车到处跑；
例句：
  1. Compare machine, tool, etc.
     试比较machine 、 tool等词.
  2. Grindingcutter, reamer, disc tool, gear shaper cutter, slide way of machine tool and tool guide.
     铣刀 、 铰刀 、 盘形车刀 、 插齿刀 、 机床导轨和刀架.
  3. Metal processing exhibition area: metal cutting machine tool, metal shaping machine tool, special processing machine tool.
     展品范围*金属加工展区: 金属切削机床 、 金属成型机床 、 特种加工机床.
  4. There are many tools in my tool storage unit ( tool chest, tool box ).
     我的工具柜 ( 工具盒 、 工具箱 ) 里面有很多工具.
  5. Tool Name: Specifies the name of the tool ( Linker Tool ).
     工具名称: 指定工具的名称 ( 链接器工具 ).
</tool>

<project>单词：project
意义：
   n.   项目，工程；计划，规划；（学生的）课题；
   vi.   伸出，突出；
   vt.   放映；计划；发射；展现，使突出；
例句：
  1. Critical Chain; Project Process Management; Project Scheduling; Project Control; Buffer setting.
     关键链; 项目进度管理; 项目进度计划; 项目进度控制; 缓冲区.
  2. Develop Project Charter C developing the project charter that formally authorizes a project or a project phase.
     1制定项目章程-制定项目章程,正式批准项目或项目阶段.
  3. GNC - PROJECT is developed basing on MS.
     GNC-PROJECT是基于微软.
  4. In the resulting Add Project Output Group dialog box, select a project from the Project list.
     在产生的“添加项目输出组”对话框中, 从“项目”列表中选择一个项目.
  5. The Close Project process involves performing the project closure portion of the project management plan.
     项目收尾过程是实施项目管理计划中的项目收尾部分.
</project>

<word>单词：word
意义：
   n.   单词；话语；诺言；消息；
   vi.   讲话；
   vt.   措辞，用词；用言语表达；
例句：
  1. Also, make your resume available in several formats -- text only , Microsoft Word a PDF.
     另外, 要确保你的简历要有几个版本 ― 纯文字 、 Word档、PDF档.
  2. Runs on Microsoft Word: You do not have to handle several windows on the screen.
     运行在微软Word中: 你不必在桌面上操作多个窗口.
  3. This file is on the PDF file format into WORD document format.
     此文件是关于把PDF文件格式转换成WORD文件格式的.
  4. Using Servers controller to call Word to create templates , which can create Word documents.
     用Servers控件调用Word能够较好地实现Delphi对Word的控制.
  5. We WORD file on a comprehensive test.
     对WORD档我们进行了全方位的测试.
</word>

<not>单词：not
意义：
   adv.   不；[用以表示否定、否认、拒绝、禁止等]不是；几乎不；未必，没有[用于否定后面的词或短语]；
例句：
  1. Bitmapped indexes are only useful equality queries, especially in combination with AND, OR, and NOT operators.
     位图索引仅对确定值的查询有效, 尤其是拥有AND, OR和NOT逻辑运算符的组合.
  2. In conversational English " is not " often contracts to " isn't ".
     口头英语中is not 常缩写为 isn ‘ t.
  3. To find rows that do not match a value, use the NOT operator.
     若要查找与某值不匹配的行, 可使用NOT运算符.
  4. We are not living for material stuff, not money, not fancy clothes, not certificates, not authority.
     我们生存在这个世界上,不是为了物质, 不是为了金钱, 不是为了华丽的衣裳, 不是为了证书, 不是为了权力.
  5. You can apply AND, OR, or NOT to boolean values only.
     只可将AND, OR或NOT应用于布尔值.
</not>

<window>单词：window
意义：
   n.   窗，窗户；窗口；〈美俚〉眼镜；
例句：
  1. A Window object is created automatically with every instance of a tag.
     Window对象将通过标签自动创建.
  2. Description: Ningbo Hengte Auto ---- Power window , motor, window regulator window , window lock automatic control.
     汽车电动玻璃升降器电机 、 总成 、车窗智能控制器.
  3. Server - side control by the game window, window board and the other 3 sub - window information constitutes window.
     服务器端主要由游戏控制窗口 、 棋盘窗口和对方信息窗口3个子窗口构成.
  4. Use window. create Popup display menu, so only use IE.
     使用window. createPopup显示菜单, 所以只能在IE中使用.
  5. Window firewall and network packet technology intercepted a source of a book, a source code.
     Window防火墙与网络封包截获技术一书配套源程序的源代码1.
</window>

<edit>单词：edit
意义：
   n.   编辑；
   vt.   剪辑（影片，录音）；编辑；校订；主编；
例句：
  1. CMD instead of a saris of manipulation comnands, as RENMAE, EDIT, COBOL, LINK, ect.
     CMD文件便可取代一系列的键控命令, 如RENAME 、 EDIT 、 COBOL 、 LINK等.
  2. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  3. The process of edit check includes edit check specifications design, edit check programming, validation and implementation.
     编辑检查步骤包括:制定编辑检查清单 、 对编辑检查进行编程和验证、运行编辑检查.
  4. Thetree edit distance problem is to compute the edit distance and a corresponding edIt'script.
     树编辑距离的问题是计算编辑距离和相应的修改脚本.
  5. Tree edit distance Assume that we are given a cost function defined on each edit operation.
     树编辑距离假定我们会得到一个成本函数定义每个编辑作业.
</edit>

<label>单词：label
意义：
   n.   标签；称标记，符号；[建] 门或窗户上面的线脚；
   vt.   贴标签于；把…称为；把…列为；[化]用放射性元素使（元素或原子等）示踪；
例句：
  1. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  2. Format of output is simple. Each line contains a label corresponding to your file.
     输出的格式很简单, 每行一个label,对应到你file里面的各行.
  3. Format of output is simple. Each line contains a label corresponding to your test _ file.
     输出的格式很简单, 每行一个label,对应到你test_file里面的各行.
  4. Label display is of single label and full label.
     标牌显示分单标牌和全标牌.
  5. Miyyo label can print packaging label , logistic label, address label, retailing label, and bar code label, etc.
     适用于外箱标签, 物流标签, 地址标签, 服装标签, 条形码标签, 等等.
</label>

<button>单词：button
意义：
   n.   按钮，电钮；纽扣，扣子；扣状物；[植]芽；
   vi.   扣住；装有钮扣；扣上钮扣；
   vt.   用纽扣扣紧；用纽扣装饰，钉钮扣于；在…上装钮扣；
例句：
  1. " N " is a syllabic consonant in " button " .
     在 button 这个词里n是 构成音节的辅音.
  2. Button icons, a default button, HTML in a button, and button mnemonics.
     按钮图标, 默认按钮, HTML格式的按钮, 按钮助记符.
  3. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  4. There is no need to subclass Button to react to events.
     而并没有必要去继承Button类来实现对于事件的响应.
  5. This example describes how to dynamically create a BUTTON control.
     本实例介绍如何动态创建BUTTON控件.
</button>

<picture>单词：picture
意义：
   n.   照片，画像；图画，图片；影片；情景；
   vt.   构想，想象；描绘，画；描述；
例句：
  1. " Movie " is a colloquial word for " moving picture " .
     movie是moving picture 的口语体.
  2. Can zoom picture processing. Can open the picture, the general picture of the operation.
     可以对图片进行放大缩小等处理. 还能打开图片, 对图片进行一般的操作.
  3. Chinese generation has many fishery to produce picture in brick of picture stone, picture.
     汉代画像石 、 画像砖中有不少渔业生产图像.
  4. In facsimile, a picture having a range of tones lying between picture black and picture white.
     在传真技术中, 具有一系列处在图象黑电平与白电平之间色调的图象.
  5. Movement picture and static picture picture nature improvement circuit.
     运动画面和静态画面的画质改善电路.
</picture>

<debug>单词：debug
意义：
   vt.   拆除窃听器；排除故障；
例句：
  1. By default, this check box is selected, specifying that a DEBUG constant be set.
     默认情况下, 选中此复选框以指定设置一个DEBUG常数.
  2. DEBUG detailed explanation of the command line parameters, including format and uses the details.
     详细的DEBUG命令行参数解释, 包含格式及用途、细节等.
  3. Return the defect boards to Debug to repair.
     10把板退还Debug去维修.
  4. This paper presents commands of DEBUG and its applications in system maintenance.
     介绍了debug命令 的作用和它在系统维护中的几项应用.
  5. We'll use DEBUG to look at a floppy disk's Boot Record.
     我们将使用DEBUG来看看软盘的引导记录.
</debug>

<video>单词：video
意义：
   adj.   电视的；视频的；影像的；用录像磁带[录像带]的；
   n.   磁带录像；录像磁带；录像机，电视；（指方法）录像；
   vt.   录像；制作…的录像；
例句：
  1. Digital video quality assessment plays important roles in video compression, visual processing and video communications.
     数字视频质量评估在视频压缩 、 处理以及视频通信领域中起着十分重要的作用.
  2. It includes: Video decoding ^ Video collection Video quantizer digital video compression and USB interface.
     它包括: 视频图像解码、视频采集、量化以及数字视频图像的压缩和USB的接口.
  3. Original Han Geng personal video, and Han Geng - related video, and gift videos, Wang video.
     原创韩庚个人视频, 与韩庚相关视频以及贺礼视频, 王道视频.
  4. View Video in detached window. Video will continue to play without restart. Support all video formats.
     把视频弹出到独立窗口继续播放,支持所有格式视频.
  5. You can customize video profiles video and parameters for output video.
     您可以自定义视频简介视频和参数视频输出.
</video>

<document>单词：document
意义：
   n.   （计算机）文档，证件；公文；
   vt.   证明；记录；为…提供证明；
例句：
  1. Accomplish the task of document tracking and document signing, responsible for document quantity and success rate.
     完成经理布置的追单、签单工作, 对追单数量和成功率负责.
  2. Bribery crime objective important document namely constitution important document, include criminal object and crime objective aspect.
     受贿罪的客观要件即客观的构成要件, 包括犯罪客体和犯罪的客观方面.
  3. Thchnical bidding document is an important document invite tenders.
     招标采购中技术标书是很重要的文件.
  4. This paper discusses the definition of network document , introduces the characteristics document, analyzes the classification document.
     本文提出了“网络文献”这一概念,对其含义 、 特点 、 类型进行了分析说明.
  5. Which is this document, document to bearer or document to order?
     这是哪一种文件, 持票人文件或指示文件?
</document>

<desktop>单词：desktop
意义：
   n.   桌面；
例句：
  1. Business card ( desktop ) small press: are usually placed on the table, called a desktop small press.
     咭片 ( 台式 ) 小胶印机: 凡是不收在桌子上, 因此称为台式小胶印机.
  2. Desktop navigation is a free personalized mobile desktop software a software integration of many ultra - functional.
     桌面导航是一个免费的个性化的移动桌面软件,软件集成了许多超功能.
  3. Desktop shortcuts save in the desktop folder, which complies with the 8.3 naming convention.
     保存在desktop文件夹中的桌面快捷方式遵守8.3命名惯例.
  4. Get freetree for your desktop. Decorate your desktop Christmas tree.
     特别提醒,鼠标放到圣诞树上面有倒计时.
  5. To open Remote Desktop Connection, click Start, point to Communications, and then click Remote Desktop Connection.
     出现“远程桌面连接”对话框.在标题栏的左上角单击计算机图标, 然后单击“关于”.
</desktop>

<generate>单词：generate
意义：
   vt.   形成，造成；产生物理反应；产生（后代）；引起；
例句：
  1. A small utility to generate robust passwords with options.
     一个小实用程序将与选择产生柔韧的口令.
  2. The compiler knows what processor it is running and can generate code specifically for that processor.
     JIT编译器知道什么处理器正在运行,可以产生对应此处理器的优化代码.
  3. These checks are disabled by default as they generate a host of warnings.
     这些检查默认都是被关闭的,因为他们通常会产生大量的警告.
  4. To generate capital appreciation with regular income.
     资本增值及赚取定期收入.
  5. Using random number generator to generate a command line.
     用随机数产生器生成一个指令系列.
</generate>

<help>单词：help
意义：
   int.   [呼救语]救命！；
   n.   帮助；助手；补救办法；有用；
   vi.   （在餐桌旁）招待，侍应，作仆人（或店员、服务员等）；
   vt.   治疗；避免；招待（客人）；给…盛（饭、菜）；
   vt.&amp; vi.   帮助；有助于， 有利于；
例句：
  1. Financial assistance is available for eligible students through the OS - HELP Scheme of Monash Abroad.
     符合有关条件的同学可以通过OS -HELP 计划向蒙纳士留学办公室申请经济援助.
  2. Online help: Get help fast using the online help feature.
     在线帮助: 快速获得帮助使用联机帮助功能.
  3. Out of memory. Type HELP MEMORY for your options.
     内存不足. 键入help内存,您的选择.
  4. People really need help but may attack you ig you do help them. Help people anyway.
     人闪需要帮助,可当你向他们伸出援助之手时,可能会反被其伤,但是不管怎样,还是要帮助他们.
  5. People really need help but may attack youyou do help them. Help people anyway.
     别人急需帮忙,你帮了忙以后竟然被他们攻击. ――不管怎样,还是要助人.
</help>

<select>单词：select
意义：
   adj.   精选的；挑选出来的；苛择的；〈口〉爱挑三拣四的，挑剔的；
   vt.   选择；挑选；选拔；
例句：
  1. For each instance of an HTML tag on a form, a Select object is created.
     它将为表单中的每个HTML标签实例创建一个select对象.
  2. Select some files or directories, and then create the ISO based on these files . 10.
     select一些文件或目录, 然后创建国际标准化组织的基础上这些文件.
  3. Select the listing by number, then press select to open it.
     通过号码来选定列表, 然后按Select打开它.
  4. The SELECT statement is used to select data from a database.
     选择语句[SELECT]是用来从一个数据库中选取数据的.
  5. When you finish enter one line, press select to save and exit that line.
     输完一行后, 按Select保存并退出该行.
</select>

<url>单词：url
意义：
   abbr.   ultraviolet light 紫外线；user requirements language 用户需求语言；
例句：
  1. A powerful URL - mapping component that lets you build applications that have comprehensible and searchable URLs.
     拥有更大的URL映射组件,这使得你构建的应用程序的URL易于理解并便于搜索.
  2. Composer can't open the URL'XX'. You must enter an absolute URL or an absolute pathname.
     编写器无法打开url'XX '. 必须输入绝对路径url或绝对路径名.
  3. Generate a sample URL in the URL Builder and create a simple spreadsheet formula.
     生成一个样本中的URL网址构建和创建一个简单的电子表格的公式.
  4. The URL parameter may be either a relative or complete URL.
     URL可以是绝对路径或是相对的路径.
  5. You'll have a customized URL to make accessing your PC a snap.
     你能自定义的URL为了使你的个人计算机能够被立刻访问.
</url>

<download>单词：download
意义：
   v.   将（程序，资料等）从大计算机系统输入小计算机系统，下载；
例句：
  1. After the designment of the application paper discuss the download software aimed at the download problem.
     在应用程序软件设计完成之后,又针对应用程序的下载问题进行了下载烧录软件的设计.
  2. Download Instructions: Visit their official website to download this application.
     下载说明: 访问其官方网站上下载此应用程序.
  3. Download here. Suggest using Flashget or some other software to download.
     点击这里开始下载, 建议用迅雷等软件进行下载.
  4. Up and Download C Accelerate Download and Upload.
     和下载-加速下载和上传.
  5. Your download will not be encrypted. Protocol Obstrucation is to overcome ISP blocking of Emule download.
     简单的说,我下载的文件内容会被加密,是这样的吗?
</download>
