<tool>单词：tool
意义：
   n.   器具，工具；（有助于做工或完成某事的）用具；受人利用的人；压印机；
   vi.   使用工具；开车，乘车；
   vt.   用工具给…加工；压印；驾车到处跑；
例句：
  1. Compare machine, tool, etc.
     试比较machine 、 tool等词.
  2. Grindingcutter, reamer, disc tool, gear shaper cutter, slide way of machine tool and tool guide.
     铣刀 、 铰刀 、 盘形车刀 、 插齿刀 、 机床导轨和刀架.
  3. Metal processing exhibition area: metal cutting machine tool, metal shaping machine tool, special processing machine tool.
     展品范围*金属加工展区: 金属切削机床 、 金属成型机床 、 特种加工机床.
  4. There are many tools in my tool storage unit ( tool chest, tool box ).
     我的工具柜 ( 工具盒 、 工具箱 ) 里面有很多工具.
  5. Tool Name: Specifies the name of the tool ( Linker Tool ).
     工具名称: 指定工具的名称 ( 链接器工具 ).
</tool>

<project>单词：project
意义：
   n.   项目，工程；计划，规划；（学生的）课题；
   vi.   伸出，突出；
   vt.   放映；计划；发射；展现，使突出；
例句：
  1. Critical Chain; Project Process Management; Project Scheduling; Project Control; Buffer setting.
     关键链; 项目进度管理; 项目进度计划; 项目进度控制; 缓冲区.
  2. Develop Project Charter C developing the project charter that formally authorizes a project or a project phase.
     1制定项目章程-制定项目章程,正式批准项目或项目阶段.
  3. GNC - PROJECT is developed basing on MS.
     GNC-PROJECT是基于微软.
  4. In the resulting Add Project Output Group dialog box, select a project from the Project list.
     在产生的“添加项目输出组”对话框中, 从“项目”列表中选择一个项目.
  5. The Close Project process involves performing the project closure portion of the project management plan.
     项目收尾过程是实施项目管理计划中的项目收尾部分.
</project>

<word>单词：word
意义：
   n.   单词；话语；诺言；消息；
   vi.   讲话；
   vt.   措辞，用词；用言语表达；
例句：
  1. Also, make your resume available in several formats -- text only , Microsoft Word a PDF.
     另外, 要确保你的简历要有几个版本 ― 纯文字 、 Word档、PDF档.
  2. Runs on Microsoft Word: You do not have to handle several windows on the screen.
     运行在微软Word中: 你不必在桌面上操作多个窗口.
  3. This file is on the PDF file format into WORD document format.
     此文件是关于把PDF文件格式转换成WORD文件格式的.
  4. Using Servers controller to call Word to create templates , which can create Word documents.
     用Servers控件调用Word能够较好地实现Delphi对Word的控制.
  5. We WORD file on a comprehensive test.
     对WORD档我们进行了全方位的测试.
</word>

<not>单词：not
意义：
   adv.   不；[用以表示否定、否认、拒绝、禁止等]不是；几乎不；未必，没有[用于否定后面的词或短语]；
例句：
  1. Bitmapped indexes are only useful equality queries, especially in combination with AND, OR, and NOT operators.
     位图索引仅对确定值的查询有效, 尤其是拥有AND, OR和NOT逻辑运算符的组合.
  2. In conversational English " is not " often contracts to " isn't ".
     口头英语中is not 常缩写为 isn ‘ t.
  3. To find rows that do not match a value, use the NOT operator.
     若要查找与某值不匹配的行, 可使用NOT运算符.
  4. We are not living for material stuff, not money, not fancy clothes, not certificates, not authority.
     我们生存在这个世界上,不是为了物质, 不是为了金钱, 不是为了华丽的衣裳, 不是为了证书, 不是为了权力.
  5. You can apply AND, OR, or NOT to boolean values only.
     只可将AND, OR或NOT应用于布尔值.
</not>

<window>单词：window
意义：
   n.   窗，窗户；窗口；〈美俚〉眼镜；
例句：
  1. A Window object is created automatically with every instance of a tag.
     Window对象将通过标签自动创建.
  2. Description: Ningbo Hengte Auto ---- Power window , motor, window regulator window , window lock automatic control.
     汽车电动玻璃升降器电机 、 总成 、车窗智能控制器.
  3. Server - side control by the game window, window board and the other 3 sub - window information constitutes window.
     服务器端主要由游戏控制窗口 、 棋盘窗口和对方信息窗口3个子窗口构成.
  4. Use window. create Popup display menu, so only use IE.
     使用window. createPopup显示菜单, 所以只能在IE中使用.
  5. Window firewall and network packet technology intercepted a source of a book, a source code.
     Window防火墙与网络封包截获技术一书配套源程序的源代码1.
</window>

<edit>单词：edit
意义：
   n.   编辑；
   vt.   剪辑（影片，录音）；编辑；校订；主编；
例句：
  1. CMD instead of a saris of manipulation comnands, as RENMAE, EDIT, COBOL, LINK, ect.
     CMD文件便可取代一系列的键控命令, 如RENAME 、 EDIT 、 COBOL 、 LINK等.
  2. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  3. The process of edit check includes edit check specifications design, edit check programming, validation and implementation.
     编辑检查步骤包括:制定编辑检查清单 、 对编辑检查进行编程和验证、运行编辑检查.
  4. Thetree edit distance problem is to compute the edit distance and a corresponding edIt'script.
     树编辑距离的问题是计算编辑距离和相应的修改脚本.
  5. Tree edit distance Assume that we are given a cost function defined on each edit operation.
     树编辑距离假定我们会得到一个成本函数定义每个编辑作业.
</edit>

<label>单词：label
意义：
   n.   标签；称标记，符号；[建] 门或窗户上面的线脚；
   vt.   贴标签于；把…称为；把…列为；[化]用放射性元素使（元素或原子等）示踪；
例句：
  1. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  2. Format of output is simple. Each line contains a label corresponding to your file.
     输出的格式很简单, 每行一个label,对应到你file里面的各行.
  3. Format of output is simple. Each line contains a label corresponding to your test _ file.
     输出的格式很简单, 每行一个label,对应到你test_file里面的各行.
  4. Label display is of single label and full label.
     标牌显示分单标牌和全标牌.
  5. Miyyo label can print packaging label , logistic label, address label, retailing label, and bar code label, etc.
     适用于外箱标签, 物流标签, 地址标签, 服装标签, 条形码标签, 等等.
</label>

<button>单词：button
意义：
   n.   按钮，电钮；纽扣，扣子；扣状物；[植]芽；
   vi.   扣住；装有钮扣；扣上钮扣；
   vt.   用纽扣扣紧；用纽扣装饰，钉钮扣于；在…上装钮扣；
例句：
  1. " N " is a syllabic consonant in " button " .
     在 button 这个词里n是 构成音节的辅音.
  2. Button icons, a default button, HTML in a button, and button mnemonics.
     按钮图标, 默认按钮, HTML格式的按钮, 按钮助记符.
  3. Create a new application, and add two Label controls, three Edit controls, four Button button.
     新建一个应用程序, 并添加两个Label控件, 三个Edit控件, 四个Button按钮.
  4. There is no need to subclass Button to react to events.
     而并没有必要去继承Button类来实现对于事件的响应.
  5. This example describes how to dynamically create a BUTTON control.
     本实例介绍如何动态创建BUTTON控件.
</button>

<picture>单词：picture
意义：
   n.   照片，画像；图画，图片；影片；情景；
   vt.   构想，想象；描绘，画；描述；
例句：
  1. " Movie " is a colloquial word for " moving picture " .
     movie是moving picture 的口语体.
  2. Can zoom picture processing. Can open the picture, the general picture of the operation.
     可以对图片进行放大缩小等处理. 还能打开图片, 对图片进行一般的操作.
  3. Chinese generation has many fishery to produce picture in brick of picture stone, picture.
     汉代画像石 、 画像砖中有不少渔业生产图像.
  4. In facsimile, a picture having a range of tones lying between picture black and picture white.
     在传真技术中, 具有一系列处在图象黑电平与白电平之间色调的图象.
  5. Movement picture and static picture picture nature improvement circuit.
     运动画面和静态画面的画质改善电路.
</picture>

<debug>单词：debug
意义：
   vt.   拆除窃听器；排除故障；
例句：
  1. By default, this check box is selected, specifying that a DEBUG constant be set.
     默认情况下, 选中此复选框以指定设置一个DEBUG常数.
  2. DEBUG detailed explanation of the command line parameters, including format and uses the details.
     详细的DEBUG命令行参数解释, 包含格式及用途、细节等.
  3. Return the defect boards to Debug to repair.
     10把板退还Debug去维修.
  4. This paper presents commands of DEBUG and its applications in system maintenance.
     介绍了debug命令 的作用和它在系统维护中的几项应用.
  5. We'll use DEBUG to look at a floppy disk's Boot Record.
     我们将使用DEBUG来看看软盘的引导记录.
</debug>

<video>单词：video
意义：
   adj.   电视的；视频的；影像的；用录像磁带[录像带]的；
   n.   磁带录像；录像磁带；录像机，电视；（指方法）录像；
   vt.   录像；制作…的录像；
例句：
  1. Digital video quality assessment plays important roles in video compression, visual processing and video communications.
     数字视频质量评估在视频压缩 、 处理以及视频通信领域中起着十分重要的作用.
  2. It includes: Video decoding ^ Video collection Video quantizer digital video compression and USB interface.
     它包括: 视频图像解码、视频采集、量化以及数字视频图像的压缩和USB的接口.
  3. Original Han Geng personal video, and Han Geng - related video, and gift videos, Wang video.
     原创韩庚个人视频, 与韩庚相关视频以及贺礼视频, 王道视频.
  4. View Video in detached window. Video will continue to play without restart. Support all video formats.
     把视频弹出到独立窗口继续播放,支持所有格式视频.
  5. You can customize video profiles video and parameters for output video.
     您可以自定义视频简介视频和参数视频输出.
</video>

<document>单词：document
意义：
   n.   （计算机）文档，证件；公文；
   vt.   证明；记录；为…提供证明；
例句：
  1. Accomplish the task of document tracking and document signing, responsible for document quantity and success rate.
     完成经理布置的追单、签单工作, 对追单数量和成功率负责.
  2. Bribery crime objective important document namely constitution important document, include criminal object and crime objective aspect.
     受贿罪的客观要件即客观的构成要件, 包括犯罪客体和犯罪的客观方面.
  3. Thchnical bidding document is an important document invite tenders.
     招标采购中技术标书是很重要的文件.
  4. This paper discusses the definition of network document , introduces the characteristics document, analyzes the classification document.
     本文提出了“网络文献”这一概念,对其含义 、 特点 、 类型进行了分析说明.
  5. Which is this document, document to bearer or document to order?
     这是哪一种文件, 持票人文件或指示文件?
</document>

<desktop>单词：desktop
意义：
   n.   桌面；
例句：
  1. Business card ( desktop ) small press: are usually placed on the table, called a desktop small press.
     咭片 ( 台式 ) 小胶印机: 凡是不收在桌子上, 因此称为台式小胶印机.
  2. Desktop navigation is a free personalized mobile desktop software a software integration of many ultra - functional.
     桌面导航是一个免费的个性化的移动桌面软件,软件集成了许多超功能.
  3. Desktop shortcuts save in the desktop folder, which complies with the 8.3 naming convention.
     保存在desktop文件夹中的桌面快捷方式遵守8.3命名惯例.
  4. Get freetree for your desktop. Decorate your desktop Christmas tree.
     特别提醒,鼠标放到圣诞树上面有倒计时.
  5. To open Remote Desktop Connection, click Start, point to Communications, and then click Remote Desktop Connection.
     出现“远程桌面连接”对话框.在标题栏的左上角单击计算机图标, 然后单击“关于”.
</desktop>

<generate>单词：generate
意义：
   vt.   形成，造成；产生物理反应；产生（后代）；引起；
例句：
  1. A small utility to generate robust passwords with options.
     一个小实用程序将与选择产生柔韧的口令.
  2. The compiler knows what processor it is running and can generate code specifically for that processor.
     JIT编译器知道什么处理器正在运行,可以产生对应此处理器的优化代码.
  3. These checks are disabled by default as they generate a host of warnings.
     这些检查默认都是被关闭的,因为他们通常会产生大量的警告.
  4. To generate capital appreciation with regular income.
     资本增值及赚取定期收入.
  5. Using random number generator to generate a command line.
     用随机数产生器生成一个指令系列.
</generate>

<help>单词：help
意义：
   int.   [呼救语]救命！；
   n.   帮助；助手；补救办法；有用；
   vi.   （在餐桌旁）招待，侍应，作仆人（或店员、服务员等）；
   vt.   治疗；避免；招待（客人）；给…盛（饭、菜）；
   vt.&amp; vi.   帮助；有助于， 有利于；
例句：
  1. Financial assistance is available for eligible students through the OS - HELP Scheme of Monash Abroad.
     符合有关条件的同学可以通过OS -HELP 计划向蒙纳士留学办公室申请经济援助.
  2. Online help: Get help fast using the online help feature.
     在线帮助: 快速获得帮助使用联机帮助功能.
  3. Out of memory. Type HELP MEMORY for your options.
     内存不足. 键入help内存,您的选择.
  4. People really need help but may attack you ig you do help them. Help people anyway.
     人闪需要帮助,可当你向他们伸出援助之手时,可能会反被其伤,但是不管怎样,还是要帮助他们.
  5. People really need help but may attack youyou do help them. Help people anyway.
     别人急需帮忙,你帮了忙以后竟然被他们攻击. ――不管怎样,还是要助人.
</help>

<url>单词：url
意义：
   abbr.   ultraviolet light 紫外线；user requirements language 用户需求语言；
例句：
  1. A powerful URL - mapping component that lets you build applications that have comprehensible and searchable URLs.
     拥有更大的URL映射组件,这使得你构建的应用程序的URL易于理解并便于搜索.
  2. Composer can't open the URL'XX'. You must enter an absolute URL or an absolute pathname.
     编写器无法打开url'XX '. 必须输入绝对路径url或绝对路径名.
  3. Generate a sample URL in the URL Builder and create a simple spreadsheet formula.
     生成一个样本中的URL网址构建和创建一个简单的电子表格的公式.
  4. The URL parameter may be either a relative or complete URL.
     URL可以是绝对路径或是相对的路径.
  5. You'll have a customized URL to make accessing your PC a snap.
     你能自定义的URL为了使你的个人计算机能够被立刻访问.
</url>

<download>单词：download
意义：
   v.   将（程序，资料等）从大计算机系统输入小计算机系统，下载；
例句：
  1. After the designment of the application paper discuss the download software aimed at the download problem.
     在应用程序软件设计完成之后,又针对应用程序的下载问题进行了下载烧录软件的设计.
  2. Download Instructions: Visit their official website to download this application.
     下载说明: 访问其官方网站上下载此应用程序.
  3. Download here. Suggest using Flashget or some other software to download.
     点击这里开始下载, 建议用迅雷等软件进行下载.
  4. Up and Download C Accelerate Download and Upload.
     和下载-加速下载和上传.
  5. Your download will not be encrypted. Protocol Obstrucation is to overcome ISP blocking of Emule download.
     简单的说,我下载的文件内容会被加密,是这样的吗?
</download>

<padding>单词：padding
意义：
   n.   衬料；衬垫；赘语；废话；
   v.   给…装衬垫，加垫子( pad的现在分词 )；步行，放轻脚步走；
例句：
  1. Compress the injury with padding and a bandage.
     用敷料和绷带加压包扎受伤肢体.
  2. Dead Room: This has major padding on the walls and ceiling, with a carpet floor.
     消声室: 它有非常专业的填充物在墙壁和天花板上, 还有地毯.
  3. Padding is specified in the order Left, Top, Right, and Bottom.
     按照左 、 上 、 右和下的顺序指定边距.
  4. Pockets of silence are better than padding an interview with random babble.
     片刻间歇的缄默比用胡说八道填充面试要更好.
  5. Therefore, arrays cannot contain padding, though the elements within the arrays may contain padding.
     因此, 数组不可能包含填充, 但数组内部的元素可以包含填充.
</padding>

<margin>单词：margin
意义：
   n.   边缘，范围；极限；利润，盈余；（版心外）的空白；
   vt.   留边；成为…的边；加边于，围绕；为…加旁注；
例句：
  1. Collateral securities obtained in connection with customer margin purchases margin purchase and short sale business.
     办理有价证券买卖融资融券业务取得之融资买进担保证券.
  2. Future gross margin , net interest margin will continue to maintain a high level.
     未来毛利率 、 净利率仍将维持较高水平.
  3. Margin: Also sign Margin Agreement below.
     融资融券: 并请签署下文融资融券合约.
  4. The margin of business enterprise can is divided into ownership share margin and obligation margin.
     企业的融资可分为股权融资和债务融资.
  5. White space around image area of a page margin, head margin, foredgemargin and foot margin respectively.
     页内围绕印纹面积的空白位.分别为内白边, 头白边,外白边和脚白边.
</margin>

<music>单词：music
意义：
   n.   音乐；乐曲；乐谱；乐队；
例句：
  1. Computer simulation experiments with MUSIC algorithm demonstrate the above conclusion is corrective.
     结合MUSIC算法完成了方位信息的提取并进行了计算机仿真实验,证明了结论的正确性.
  2. Extended - order cross - correlation matrix based MUSIC method and its performance in non - Gaussian and color noise are discussed.
     讨论了一种基于正弦信号扩阶 互相关 矩阵的MUSIC算法及其在 非 高斯有色噪声下的性能.
  3. Separately on the beam element domain and the domain MUSIC algorithm comparison.
     分别对波束域和阵元域MUSIC算法进行比较.
  4. The mathematics model of MUSIC at subarray level was proposed and simplified array manifolds were adopted.
     提出了子阵级MUSIC的数学模型并应用了简化的阵列流形.
  5. The voice mode is surely a low frequency rolloff, so use the lowest number music mode.
     “Voice”模式是一个完全的低频滚降, 所以用最小级数的“Music”模式.
</music>

<musical>单词：musical
意义：
   adj.   音乐的，用于音乐的；喜爱[精通]音乐的；音调优美的；悦耳的；
   n.   （社交性的）音乐会；[影视]歌舞片；音乐（喜）剧 = musical comedy；
例句：
  1. Also, he was in a musical before so he also known as a musical actor.
     而且, 他曾参演过音乐片,所以他也以音乐片演员而闻名.
  2. Mr. Huang Zi is a famous musical educator, artist and musician theoretically Chinese recent musical history.
     黄自先生是我国近现代音乐史上一位著名的音乐教育家 、 作曲家和音乐理论家.
  3. Such musical instrument can make musical sounds.
     这种乐器能奏出悦耳的声音.
  4. The musical ability is the precondition of success to persons who attend in musical activity.
     音乐能力是从事音乐活动的人能否获得成功的先决条件.
  5. The musical theater company is about to launch a new performer on the musical world.
     这家音乐公司即将向音乐界推出一位新人.
</musical>

<ka>单词：ka
意义：
   n.   （古埃及人或偶像的）灵魂，鬼魂，阴灵；
例句：
  1. Jim Ryun ( R - KA ) which would have prohibited such interchange programs with the PRC.
     JimRyum ( R-KA ) 提议的禁止中美之间的交流与合作的修正议案.
  2. Ka me, ka thee - it is a proverb all over the world.
     你帮我, 我帮你 ―― 这是举世皆知的一句谚语.
  3. Ka, ka, ka, ka, walk forward, across a red high - heeled shoe that can dance tap.
     卡 、 卡 、 卡 、 卡 、 向前走, 遇到一只会跳踢踏舞的红色高跟鞋.
  4. Ka, ka, ka, ka, walk forward, come across a blue high - heeled shoe that can dance waltz.
     卡 、 卡 、 卡 、 卡 、 向前走, 遇到一只会跳华尔兹的蓝色高跟鞋.
  5. The differences of PNA and RCA - 1 expression are useful in differential diagnosis between SCC and KA.
     PNA和 RCA -1 受体在SCC和KA中表达上的差异性可用于鉴别诊断.
</ka>

<videos>单词：videos
意义：
   n.   磁带录像( video的名词复数 )；录像磁带；录像机；（指方法）录像；
例句：
  1. Games Ask the students to watch four videos and find out the mistakes the videos.
     说明:通过游戏找错激发学生的学习兴趣,每发现一个错误加五分.
  2. MTV has launched a music service called Urge, which has downloadable music and music videos.
     MTV也推出了一项名为Urge的音乐服务, 提供音乐和音乐视频下载.
  3. Responsible mixingsound and acquisitions of developed entertainment videos and music videos for domestic and international distribution.
     负责取得优质音乐录影带、娱乐性节目等之美国本土以及全球发行权.
  4. The phones will boast new features, such as the ability to record and edit videos.
     新手机将拥有几个引以自豪的新特性, 如录制和编辑视频的功能.
  5. We extract frames from videos to classify objectionable videos with a two - tier SVM classifier.
     我们藉由从影片中撷取图片及两层式的支撑向量机架构来分类不当影片.
</videos>

<editor>单词：editor
意义：
   n.   编辑，编者；校订者；[计]编辑软件，编辑程序；
例句：
  1. Name - Editor Suffix - This is a suffix that only appears in the editor.
     名称 - 编辑器后缀 - 这是一个后缀只出现在编辑器.
  2. That is the thesis of Anatole Kaletsky an editor - at - large for The Times and a prolific commentator.
     这是阿纳托莱? 卡列茨基 ( AnatoleKaletsky )的观点.卡列茨基是《泰晤士报》(TheTimes) 的自由编辑(editor-at-large),也是一位多产的评论员.
  3. These buttons also appear on the Text Editor toolbar when a document is open in editor.
     当在编辑器中打开文档时,这些按钮还会出现在“文本编辑器”工具栏上.
  4. Translated Description : China's first online video editor, online photo editor.
     国内第一,在线视频编辑器, 在线图片编辑器.
  5. With Object Oriented Programming ( OOP ), MCM - Editor ? s modelshave been coded and debugged in Delphi 5 . O and Windows 98 operation system.
     实现了对MCM-Editor模型的面向对象编程.
</editor>

<editors>单词：editors
意义：
   n.   编辑( editor的名词复数 )；（广播电视节目的）记者；（影片、广播电视节目的）剪辑员；编辑程序；
例句：
  1. Editors are busy revising articles.
     编辑们正在忙着改稿.
  2. Text editors, graphic editors, writers, photographers, affairs department, the members of a number.
     文字编辑, 美术编辑, 文字记者, 摄影记者, 外事部 、 办公室成员若干.
  3. The editors are collating the contributions.
     编辑们在对稿件进行校雠.
  4. The synthetic qualities of editors play important role in quality and fate of a sci - tech periodical.
     编辑的综合素质高低对科技期刊的质量和命运具有重要影响.
  5. You will receive a further notice as soon as the editors have made a decision.
     你将收到一个进一步通知,编辑部已将做出决定.
</editors>

<labels>单词：labels
意义：
   n.   标签( label的名词复数 )；称号；[建筑学]（装饰于门窗上方的）披水石；[纹章学]（家族长子身份附在文件上的）带有封印的丝带；
例句：
  1. Assuring that all batch labels and other labels if damaged have been removed.
     确保已损坏的批标签和其他标签已清除.
  2. Childrenwear and Baby Garments, Knitwear and Knitted Fabrics, Labels, Stickers and Tags, Junior Apparels, Knits, Labels.
     采购产品童装和婴儿服装, 针织物和编织了织物, 标签, 标签和标签, 年少者使, 穿衣编织, 标签.
  3. D pie chart and Insert &gt; Data labels, show data labels as percentage.
     三维饼图并选择插入&gt;数据标签, 按百分比显示数据标签.
  4. Remove any product labels or Department of Transportation ( DOT ) shipping hazard labels.
     去掉产品标签或交通部 ( DOT ) 的运输危险品标志.
  5. Supervise on registration of Chinese label for imported products, private labels and bottling wine labels.
     监督进口产品的中文标签, 店标酒和灌装酒类的商标注册.
</labels>

<unit>单词：unit
意义：
   n.   单位，单元；装置；个体；[数]单位数；
例句：
  1. Northeast Soybean, Moisture per Unit 1 % Price 1 %, Admixture per Unit 1 % Price 1 %, Oil Content per Unit 1 % Price 1.5 %.
     东北大豆.水分每增减1%合同价格减增1%杂质每增减1%合同价格减增1%含油量每增减1%合同价格增减1.5%.
  2. The BSC includes receiving unit, processing unit, recording unit , and transmitting unit.
     该BSC包括 接收单元 、 处理单元 、 记录单元和发送单元.
  3. The design of DCS in HF Alkylation unit, MTBE unit and Gas Separation unit is introduced.
     介绍了氢氟酸烷基化装置 、 甲基叔丁基醚(MTBE)装置及气分装置等的DCS的设计.
  4. The hardware mainly includes power supply, signal input unit, main control unit, signal output unit.
     硬件主要由电源部分 、 信号输入单元 、 主控单元和信号输出单元等组成.
  5. The rules made a corn unit equal to a gold unit equal to a Coca - Cola unit.
     这个原则对玉米的规定和黄金, 可口可乐 都是一样的,用单位来表示.
</unit>

<units>单词：units
意义：
   n.   单位；[药剂学]（药物、疫苗、血清、抗原等的）单位( unit的名词复数 )；装置；一件（商品）；（栋公寓大楼中的一套公寓）单元；
例句：
  1. Critical units to be upgraded include fluid catalytic cracker units , cokers, ultracrackers and alkylation units.
     关键单元的升级包括液态催化裂化装置设备、炼焦器 、 超加氢裂化装置以及烷化设备.
  2. He does tremendous damage to close up units, but not much to farther away units.
     它的攻击可以对近处的单位造成巨大伤害, 不过对远处的单位却不很有效.
  3. Large units and small units includes the relationship between efficiency and fairness of the community's choice.
     大户型与小户型的关系包含着社会对效率和公平的取舍.
  4. Tape drives range in size from small cartridge units, called streaming tape units, which units.
     磁带驱动器的范围是:小墨盒单位, 称为流磁带单位, 哪个单位.
  5. The units painted on the dial of a scale are often mass units, not force units.
     秤的刻度盘上所标单位是质量的单位, 而不是力的单位.
</units>

<send>单词：send
意义：
   adj.   [仅用作定语]用于发送的；
   vi.   派遣，发出，派人；
   vt.   送；使作出（某种反应）；派遣；使进入（某状态）；
   vt.&amp; vi.   用无线电波发送，发出信息；
例句：
  1. AN EFFECT SEND and RETURN jack is also supplied to allow the use of external effectors.
     同时也提供一个SEND和RETURN插孔以允许您使用外接音响效应器.
  2. I want to send a cable first then send an invoice.
     我想先发一份电报,然后再寄张发票.
  3. If I could help, you must send me your a bank card. can you send me?
     如果我能帮你, 你必须把你的帐户卡给我邮寄过来! 你能邮寄过来 吗 ?
  4. Send money, and we shall send you books.
     寄钱来, 那么我们就会把书给您送去.
  5. To run and send a report now, first select and then click Send Now.
     要立即运行和发送报告, 请选定报告,然后单击“立即发送”.
</send>

<cpp>单词：cpp
意义：
   abbr.   coal preparation plant 选煤厂；critical path plan 临界途径计划；
例句：
  1. CONCLUSION : CPP is a new safe medical material with good compatibility.
     结论CPP材料是一种安全而理想的可吸收性生物医用材料.
  2. Infrared spectroscopy shows that grafting of aromatic group on the molecular chain of CPP is successful.
     红外谱图表明,在原来的CPP分子链 上接上了芳环基团.
  3. These are contained in the corresponding CPP document.
     这些都包含在相应的CPP文件中.
  4. This machine is used for BOPP 、 PET 、 CPP 、 Al - foil, paper rolling material for composition.
     本机适用于BOPP、PET、CPP、铝箔 、 纸张卷筒状材料的复合.
  5. With SDS - PAGE , molecular mass of CPP were measured : 3300 and 4600, respectively.
     使用SDS -PAGE 法对CPP的分子量进行测定,可以分离出分子量为4600和3300的两种多肽.
</cpp>

<corset>单词：corset
意义：
   n.   （妇女为衬托身体的）紧身胸衣；
例句：
  1. A stay is another word for corset in British English.
     在英式英语中,stay是corset的另一种表达.
  2. As tight as a corset, the new speed suits make the wearer sleeker and more streamlined.
     这种新型泳衣穿起来就像紧身胸衣, 可使穿着者身形光滑,更具流线型.
  3. Corset: Article of clothing worn to shape or constrict the torso.
     紧身健美装: 一种贴身内衣或外部装饰,使体形美观或紧束身躯用的衣物.
  4. Franc Fernandez : " There was a corset but the rest of it was skin on skin . "
     有一个紧身胸衣在里面,但它的其余部分都是 贴身 的.
  5. The hardest part was fastening the corset, which she managed after a fashion.
     按着时尚,她把腹带紧束到最难忍的部位.
</corset>

<big>单词：big
意义：
   adj.   大的；重要的；（计划）庞大的；大方的；
   adv.   大量地；成功地；夸大地；宽宏大量地；
   n.   大亨；大公司；
例句：
  1. BIG might sell its Bsian arm to another insurance firm; Prudential was not the only bidder.
     BIG也许会将其亚洲分支出售给另外一家保险公司, 保信并不是独一的竞价人.
  2. Carrie fell for the wealthy Mr. Big.
     Carrie爱上了那位富有的Big先生.
  3. In this sentence, the word BIG is in capitals.
     本句中BIG一词用的是大写字母.
  4. The word " big " has one syllable and the word " Africa " has three syllables.
     “ big ” 这个词只有一个音节而 “ Africa ” 有三个音节.
  5. There remains a tension at the heart of BIG s predicament.
     目前,BIG心里仍维持着一种紧张的态势.
</big>
